<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on 2018.lab</title>
    <link>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on 2018.lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>tracestar Concept</title>
      <link>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/tracestar-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/tracestar-concept/</guid>
      <description>Abstracts Revisiting A*, its seems there are not that many interactive experience that can immerse knowledge seeker into the algorithm. Game is a great device for this. In this spirit, the lab decided to concept tracestar, a casual game with the main goal of letting the user experience A*.
Introduction A* is a path finding algorithm optimized to find shortest and cheapest path between two points. The algorithm is a generalized case of Dijkstra&amp;rsquo;s path finding algorithm, using a heuristic, or an estimated guess as to how far away a node is from the goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAT hyperproxy conceptualize</title>
      <link>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/dat-hyperproxy-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 13:21:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/dat-hyperproxy-concept/</guid>
      <description>Abstracts This blog entails the discussion between @stayfun_ and I this Sunday on our brainstorming session for Hyperproxy.
Introduction We had a discussion with @joeahand 7 days ago regarding what we can do to most effectively contribute to the Dat project. The project we decided to work on is related to this comment that Joe left on an issue in dat-js, the original project we planned to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAT White Paper Dissection</title>
      <link>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/dat-wp-uml-dissect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 11:34:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://louisgv.me/2018/blog/dat-wp-uml-dissect/</guid>
      <description>Abstracts This is a technical log on our progress on the FOSS project. It is the second week of Sprint 1, and the Rochester weather is ever forgiving. My ankles were soaked in snow for at least three days straight, and my shoes had turned into a bleak white shade.
Our initial goal of Sprint 1 week 2 is to research and understand as much as possible about the Dat-js library as well as the DAT protocol as a whole from their white paper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>